#07 "The Receptionist Ranking"
Noir Stardia
Lizardman tail
3,500 points
50,000 points
300,000 points
Dragon fang
Unicorn horn
Lola
Sarah
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10 l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Job:  Receptionist
Skills [Charm] [Winning People Over] [Sadist]
Skills [Taking It on Your Lap (Grade A]
Skills [Straddling (Grade A)]
Skills [Sitting on Your Face (Grade A)]
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10 l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Sarah
Job:  Receptionist
Skills [Charm] [Winning People Over] [Sadist]
Skills [Taking It on Your Lap (Grade A]
Skills [Straddling (Grade A)]
Skills [Sitting on Your Face (Grade A)]
I don't want to die
Noir Stardia
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10 l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Emma Brightness
Skills [Dual-Wielded Daggers (Grade B)]
Skills [Wind Strike]
Skills [Dragonslayer]
new!
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10 l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Luna Heela
Skills [Magical Firearms (Grade B)]
Skills [Energy Shot]
Skills [Healing Shot]
Skills [Cowardice] [Lift Curse]
Skills [Dragonslayer]
new!
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10 l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Noir Stardia
Skills [Great Sage] [Get Creative] [Editor]
Skills [Bestow] [LP Conversion] [Stone Bullet]
Skills [Discerning Eye] [Headache Immunity]
Skills [Pocket Dimension (Grade C)]
Skills [Improved Back Step]
Skills [Passive Defense] [Shoulder Rub]
Skills [Lucky Lecher]
Skills [Dungeon Elevator] [Blinding Light]
Skills [Night Vision] [Dragonslayer]
new!
Beware of Dragons!
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10 l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Earth Dragon Lv.28
Skills
[Rock Breath]
[Lightning Weakness (Grade B)]
[Menace]
[Roar]
[Charge]
Earth Dragon
Skills
[Rock Breath]
[Lightning Weakness (Grade B)]
Needed to Erase
Needed to use Editor
Lola
Sarah
Noir Stardia
LP. 3000
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10 l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Noir Stardia  Lv.62
Get Creative and Make Skills
[Holy Flame] [Water Drop] [Lightning Strike]
LP. 1700
Magic Fusion
Water Drop
Stone Bullet
Lightning Strike
Holy Flame
Water Drop
Stone Bullet
Lightning Strike
Dungeon Floor 6
Alice Theater
Luna Theater
#08 "A Little Girl's Wish"
Illustration: Saeki Sola